parcelpending.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy - We Care About Your Privacy - Parcel Pending

###### 

This Privacy Policy describes how Parcel Pending, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively “Parcel Pending”) treat personal information that Parcel Pending collects and receives from you through this Website and other aspects of Parcel Pending’s business including offline.

Parcel Pending’s affiliates include without limitation the entities operating this Website.  
If you have a question whether a site is a Website of Parcel Pending, or if an entity is an affiliate of Parcel Pending, please check the information posted on the site. For other material, contact Parcel Pending at help@parcelpending.com or 855-316-4756.

ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

Each time you access, use, place an order on, or browse this Website, you signify your acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Website and must discontinue use of the Website immediately. If you provide your personal information to Parcel Pending through other aspects of Parcel Pending’s business including offline, Parcel Pending asks you to review this Privacy Policy which also governs information collected through other aspects of Parcel Pending’s business including offline.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Parcel Pending does not own or control, or to people whom Parcel Pending does not employ or manage.

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

The personal information that Parcel Pending collects about you may include without limitation your first and last name, home address, email address, home telephone number, password, credit or debit card number or other payment method, billing and shipping information, order history, preferences for products, shopping and entertainment that is not otherwise publicly available, or other data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.

Parcel Pending collects personal information about you whenever you:

  * Transact business with Parcel Pending
  * Use Parcel Pending’s products or services
  * Request information or materials
  * Enter sweepstakes, contests or drawings offered by Parcel Pending
  * Create or update a profile
  * Place orders or make purchases
  * Communicate with us about orders or other questions
  * Visit the Website

The collection of this information enables Parcel Pending to provide first class services, to keep you apprised of information and developments that you may find of interest, and to allow Parcel Pending to better understand your needs.

When you register to request information on a Website or make purchases on a Website, for example, you submit personal information that allows us to provide information about Parcel Pending that may be of interest to you. Once you register to use these features of the Website, you are not anonymous to us.

Parcel Pending may acquire personal information from vendors that may share the information as permitted in their privacy policies, or from other third parties.

Parcel Pending may combine personal information with information available from other sources (such as offline records or publicly available information). If the combined information permits us to contact you online or offline, we will treat the combined information as personal information.

COLLECTION OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Parcel Pending automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser as well as through other analysis of the Website. Non-personal information includes without limitation your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, cookie information (as described below), the pages you request, type of computer operating system you use (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the type of browser you use (e.g., Firefox, Chrome, Internet Explorer), the domain name of the Internet service provider, your activities while visiting the Website, and the content you accessed.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer. When you visit the Website, your Web browser may store cookies on your computer, which will better enable you to navigate the Website upon return. You may use the Website even if you choose to reject or delete the cookies. Cookies also may be used by the Website for which a link is placed on the Website.  
Parcel Pending’s Use of Your Personal Information Parcel Pending limits access to personal information about you by Parcel Pending employees and agents to those who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you, administer and process payments, fulfill orders, ship and confirm orders, provide customer service, update account information, post Submissions, inform you of products or services that may be of interest to you, forward updates, announcements, and newsletters, respond to your communications, and communicate with you about the Website, Communications Services, Submissions and other activities related to the Website, and you authorize Parcel Pending to transmit email to you concerning these matters.

Parcel Pending affiliates may share your personal information freely with other Parcel Pending affiliates.

DISCLOSURES TO THIRD PARTIES

Parcel Pending may provide your personal information to trusted operators who work on behalf of or with Parcel Pending under confidentiality or similar agreements including service providers, shippers, vendors, payment processors, advertisers, consultants and affiliates. These companies may use your personal information to help Parcel Pending administer its business or the Website, including but not limited to assistance in administering and processing payments, fulfilling orders, shipping and confirming orders, or communicating with you about offers or other information relevant to Parcel Pending. Consistent with this Privacy Policy, Parcel Pending may share questions or requests that you send to Parcel Pending, including those that contain personal information, with third-party so that these third parties can contact you to address your inquiries.

Except for your credit or debit card number or other payment method, Parcel Pending may also provide your personal information to selected third-party entities, including without limitation multi-family apartment communities and other businesses. Your personal information will only be shared by Parcel Pending to these strategic third-party entities to provide or improve our products and services. Parcel Pending will not share your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes, and Parcel Pending will not sell your personal information to third-parties. Parcel Pending is not responsible for the collection or maintenance of information, including with respect to your information, or other practices of any third parties.

DISCLOSURES UNDER SPECIAL CIRCUMSTANCES

Parcel Pending may provide information about you in response to or cooperate with law enforcement, government requests, subpoenas, court orders or legal process; to respond to your requests for customer service or other information; to enforce the Terms of Use; to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or to protect the safety or property of Parcel Pending or others. Parcel Pending also may provide information about you if Parcel Pending believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

MAJOR TRANSACTIONS

Parcel Pending reserves the right to transfer any and all information, including without limitation personal information, to another Parcel Pending affiliate or to a third party or successor in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or disposition of all or any portion of our business or operations (including without limitation in connection with bankruptcy or any similar proceedings).

NOTICE OF PRIVACY RIGHTS OF CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

If you are a California resident and have provided personal information to Parcel Pending, you are entitled by law to request certain information regarding any disclosure by Parcel Pending to third parties of personal information for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an email to help@parcelpending.com, specifying that you seek your “California Customer Choice Privacy Notice.” Include the website or line of business to which your request pertains. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response. Parcel Pending is required to respond to only one request per customer each year, and is not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the above email address.

We will not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes if you request that we do not do so. You may make such a request by sending us an email at help@parcelpending.com or mailing your request to 1 Vanderbilt, Irvine, CA 92618.

When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, which website or line of business to which your request pertains, and what personal information you do not want us to share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personal information or for processing this request.

USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Parcel Pending may share and disclose information that is not reasonably linked to you or your devices with third parties to show or analyze site usage, improve our services, improve our user experience, or for similar purposes. In addition, we may use your IP address to analyze trends, administer the Website and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order to improve the Website.

PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Parcel Pending understands that storing our data in a secure manner is important. Parcel Pending stores personal information using industry standard, reasonable and technically feasible, physical, technical and administrative safeguards against foreseeable risks, such as unauthorized access.

Please be aware that the Website and data storage are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond Parcel Pending’s control. Parcel Pending is not responsible for the acts and omissions of any third parties.

Parcel Pending cannot guarantee the security of the information on and sent from the Website. No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Parcel Pending to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, neither Parcel Pending nor any of our service providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the Internet. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

CORRECTING OR REMOVING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION / OPT OUT

To review or change your personal information, please send your request, including the website or line of business to which your request pertains, to help@parcelpending.com, or to 1 Vanderbilt, Irvine, CA 92618.

If you want to unsubscribe from an email list of Parcel Pending, please let us know by following the “Unsubscribe” instructions that are included in each promotional email from Parcel Pending. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective. You may not opt out of receiving communications regarding your purchases, your dealings with the Website, or technical information about the Website.

We respect your privacy. If you’d like to suppress your personal information from being shared with third-party organizations, please click on the following link “Opt-Out Request Form” to opt-out.

CHILDREN

Parcel Pending is committed to protecting the privacy of children. The Website is directed to persons 18 years of age or older. Parcel Pending and the Website do not knowingly collect information from children under age 18. If you are under age 13, you are not permitted to use the Website or to submit any personally identifiable information to the Website. If you provide information to Parcel Pending through the Website, you represent and warrant to Parcel Pending that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are 13 – 17 years of age, you may visit, browse and use the information on the Website, but you may not submit any personal information to the Website, and you represent and warrant to Parcel Pending that you have permission of your parent or guardian to use the Website and any activities on the Website, who agree to these Terms on your behalf. If we become aware that a Website user is under age 18 and has provided personal information, we will remove his or her personal information from our files. If you are a parent or guardian and believe Parcel Pending may have inadvertently collected personal information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an email, including the website or line of business to which your request pertains, to help@parcelpending.com.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

On our Website, you may have the opportunity to follow a link to other sites that may be of interest to you. Parcel Pending endeavors to only link to reputable organizations related to your areas of interest. Because these other sites may not be hosted or controlled by Parcel Pending, however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites or the content provided thereon. Therefore, the privacy policies with respect to these areas may differ from those applicable to the Website and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of each of those other sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected and maintained by Parcel Pending.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as we add new features and services, as laws change, and as industry privacy and security best practices evolve. We display an effective date on the upper left corner of the Privacy Policy so that it will be easier for you to know when there has been a change. Accordingly, you should check the Privacy Policy on a regular basis for the most current privacy practices. Each time you access, use or browse the Website, you signify your acceptance of the then-current changes to the Privacy Policy applying to your personal information collected by us on and from the effective date of such changes.

Any changes in the Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting and apply only to information collected from you on and after Last Revised date, unless we provide notice or have other communications with you.

GOVERNING LAW

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by, and will be construed under the laws of the State of California, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law principles. Those who choose to access the Website from locations outside of the United States do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws if and to the extent local laws are applicable, including without limitation, all applicable laws, rules and regulations regarding the transmission of data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside. Parcel Pending may limit a Website’s availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction, at any time in its sole discretion.

Personal information collected through the Website and other aspects of Parcel Pending’s business may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Parcel Pending or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Website, you expressly consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Policy or our Website, please contact us at help@parcelpending.com. Please note that email communications may not be secure. Accordingly, you should not include personal or other sensitive information in your email correspondence to the Website or Parcel Pending.
